Guide to the Sarenco Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, circa 1960s-2000s; Series III
  - 849-Julien Blaine performance (Box 4)
  - 850-Julien Blaine performance (Box 4)
  - 851-Julien Blaine performance (Box 4)
  - 852-Julien Blaine performance (Box 4)
  - 853-Julien Blaine performance (Box 4)
  - 854-Julien Blaine performance (Box 4)
  - 855-Julien Blaine performance (Box 4)
  - 856-Julien Blaine performance (Box 4)
  - 857-Julien Blaine performance (Box 4)
  - 858-Sarenco performance (Box 4)
  - 859-Sarenco performance (Box 4)
  - 860-Giovanni Fontana e Arrigo Lora-Totino (Box 4)
  - 861-Arrigo Lora-Totino e Giovanni Fontana (Box 4)
  - 862-Giovanni Fontana performance (Box 4)
  - 863-Arrigo Lora-Totino performance (Box 4)
  - 864-Giovanni Fontana e Arrigo Lora-Totino performance (Box 4)
  - 865-Giovanni Fontana e Arrigo Lora-Totino performance (Box 4)
  - 866-Giovanni Fontana e Arrigo Lora-Totino performance (Box 4)
  - 867-Sarenco vernissage (Box 4)
  - 868-Mauro Dal Fior performance (Box 4)
  - 869-Mauro Dal Fior performance (Box 4)
  - 870-Mauro Dal Fior performance (Box 4)
  - 871-Mauro Dal Fior performance (Box 4)
  - 872-Mauro Dal Fior performance (Box 4)
  - 873-Mauro Dal Fior performance (Box 4)
  - 874-Mauro Dal Fior performance (Box 4)
  - 875-Mauro Dal Fior performance (Box 4)
  - 876-Enzo Minarelli performance (Box 4)
  - 877-Enzo Minarelli performance (Box 4)
  - 878-Enzo Minarelli performance (Box 4)
  - 879-Enzo Minarelli performance (Box 4)
  - 880-Enzo Minarelli performance (Box 4)
  - 881-Enzo Minarelli performance (Box 4)
  - 882-Sarenco e Julien Blaine (Box 4)
  - 883-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 884-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 885-Un'opera di Giuseppe Chiari (Box 5)
  - 886-Un'opera di Paul De Vree (Box 5)
  - 887-Un'opera di Paul De Vree (Box 5)
  - 888-Una performance di Sarenco 1968 (Box 5)
  - 889-Ugo Carrega, X, Luis Prieto, Giorgio Cortenova, Guido Almansi, Egidio Mucci, Sarenco, Lamberto Pignotti, X alla Galleria d'arte moderna di Verona (Box 5)
  - 890-Una performance di Sarenco, 1968 (Box 5)
  - 891-Pierre Garnier, Ilse Garnier, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 892-Un'opera di Jiri Valoch (Box 5)
  - 893-Un'opera di Jiri Valoch (Box 5)
  - 894-Un'opera di Wolf Vostell (Box 5)
  - 895-Un'opera di Wolf Vostell (Box 5)
  - 896-Un'opera di Wolf Vostell (Box 5)
  - 897-Un'opera di Wolf Vostell (Box 5)
  - 898-Un'opera di Wolf Vostell (Box 5)
  - 899-Un'opera di Wolf Vostell (Box 5)
  - 900-Un'opera di Wolf Vostell (Box 5)
  - 901-Un'opera di Wolf Vostell (Box 5)
  - 902-Un'opera di Wolf Vostell (Box 5)
  - 903-Un'opera di Wolf Vostell (Box 5)
  - 904-Un film di Sarenco 'Benvenuto Grande Cinema' (Box 5)
  - 905-Un film di Sarenco 'Benvenuto Grande Cinema' (Box 5)
  - 906-Un film di Sarenco 'Pagana' (Box 5)
  - 907-Una performance di Sarenco, 1968 (Box 5)
  - 908-Una performance di Sarenco, 1968 (Box 5)
  - 909-Un film di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 910-Un film di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 911-Mau Mau Freedom Fighters, Meru, Kenya (Box 5)
  - 912-Un'installazione di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 913-Un film di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 914-Un film di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 915-Un film di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 916-Un film di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 917/1042- 126 foto della performance 'Intervista-Azione' di Joseph Beuys e Sarenco, realizzata nello studio di Beuys a Dusseldorf nel 1978 (Box 5)
  - 1043-Un'installazione di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1044-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1045-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1046-Un'opera di J.M. Calleja (Box 5)
  - 1047-Un'opera di J.M. Calleja (Box 5)
  - 1048-Un'opera di J.M. Calleja (Box 5)
  - 1049-Un'opera di J.M. Calleja (Box 5)
  - 1050-Un'opera di J.M. Calleja (Box 5)
  - 1051-Un'opera di J.M. Calleja (Box 5)
  - 1052-Un'opera di J.M. Calleja (Box 5)
  - 1053-Un'opera di J.M. Calleja (Box 5)
  - 1054-Un'opera di J.M. Calleja (Box 5)
  - 1055-Sarenco e Massima (Box 5)
  - 1056-Sarenco e Daniela (Box 5)
  - 1057-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1058-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1059-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1060-Munaa, Sarenco, Kismat (Box 5)
  - 1061-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1062-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1057-Karel Trinkewitz, Sarenco, Jakob De Chirico, Enrico Mascelloni (Box 5)
  - 1058-Giovanni Fontana, Sarenco, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1059-Grazia Azzaki, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1060-Sarenco, Grazia Azzali (Box 5)
  - 1061-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1062-Giovanni Fontana, Julien Blaine, Sarenco, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1063-Sarenco, Harald Szeemann (Box 5)
  - 1064-Balint Szombathy e Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1065-Balint Szombathy e Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1066-Balint Szombathy e Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1067-Balint Szombathy e Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1068-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1069-X, Enrico Mascelloni, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1070-X, Enrico Mascelloni, Sarenco, Fabrizio Garghetti (Box 5)
  - 1071-Rina Parise, Sarenco, X, Harald Szeemann, Fabrizio Garghetti (Box 5)
  - 1072-Sarenco, Alain Arias-Misson, Fiammetta, Fabrizio Garghetti (Box 5)
  - 1073-X, X, X, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1074-Fiammetta, Enrico Mascelloni, Carlo Palli, X, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1075-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1076-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1077-E.M. De Melo e Castro, Balint Szombathy, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1078-Sarenco, Harald Szeemann (Box 5)
  - 1079-Sarenco, Klaus Peter Dencker (Box 5)
  - 1080-Patrizio Peterlini, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1081-Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, Enrico Miccini, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1082-Sarenco, Demostenes Agrafiotis (Box 5)
  - 1083-Ma Desheng, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1084-Bernard Heidsieck, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1085-Sarenco, Bernard Heidsieck (Box 5)
  - 1086-Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni (Box 5)
  - 1087-Signora Palli,nSarenco, X, E.M. De Melo e Castro, Eugenio Miccini, Ito Motoyuki (Box 5)
  - 1088-Arrigo Lora-Totino, sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1089-Enrico Mascelloni, Sarenco, E.M. De Melo e Castro, X, Signora Palli (Box 5)
  - 1090-X, Julien Blaine, Sarenco, E.M. De Melo e Castro, Fernando Aguiar, Klaus Peter Dencker, Eugenio Miccini, Karel Trinkewitz, Ann Noel, Emmett Williams, X (Box 5)
  - 1091-Eugenio Miccini, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1092-Sarenco, Ma Desheng (Box 5)
  - 1093-Ramon Salvo, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1094-Sarenco, Julien Blaine, Ramon Salvo (Box 5)
  - 1095-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1096-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1097-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1098-Enrico Mascelloni, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1099-Una performance di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1100-Una performance di Sarenci (Box 5)
  - 1101-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1102-Una performance di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1103-Ladislav Novak, Gianni-Emilio Simonetti, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1104-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1105-Fabrizio Garghetti, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1106-Una performance di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1107-Anna Oberto, Ugo Carrega, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - Eugenio Miccini, X, X, Enrico Mascelloni, Sarenco, Julien Blaine, Ramon Salvo (Box 5)
  - 1108-Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, Gianni-Emilio Simonetti (Box 5)
  - 1109-Ladislav Novak, Sarenco, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1110-Ladislav Novak, Sarenco, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1111-Alain Arias-Misson, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1112-Una performance di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1113-Sarenco, Fabrizio Garghetti (Box 5)
  - 1114-Fabrizio Garghetti, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1115-Sarenco, Demostenes Agrafiotis (Box 5)
  - 1116-Una performance di Sarenco e Balint Szombathy (Box 5)
  - 1117-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1118-Enrico Mascelloni, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1119-Giovanni Fontana, Julien Blaine, Sarenco, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1120-Sarenco, Ladislav Novak (Box 5)
  - 1121-Sarenco, Michele Perfetti (Box 5)
  - 1122-Sarenco, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1123-X,X,X, Sarenco, Paolo Berardelli (Box 5)
  - 1124-Sarenco, Achille Bonito Oliva (Box 5)
  - 1125-Enrico Mascelloni, X, Sarenco, Giorgio Olivieri (Box 5)
  - 1126-Sarenco,X, Francesco Conz (Box 5)
  - 1127-Balint Szombathy e Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1128-Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, Fabrizio Garghetti (Box 5)
  - 1129-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1130-Un'installazione di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1131-Alain Arias-Misson, X, Sarenco, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1132-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1133-Barbara Grimani, Sarenco, X (Box 5)
  - 1134-Luigi Bonotto, X, Sarenco, Barbara Grimani, Fabrizio Dal Santo, X (Box 5)
  - 1135-Enrico Mascelloni, Martina Corgnati, X, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1136-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1137-Sarenco, Ladislav Novak (Box 5)
  - 1138-Karel Trinkewitz, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1139-Alain Arias-Misson, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1140-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1141-Valerio Dehò, Enrico Mascelloni, X, Sarenco, Carlo Palli (Box 5)
  - 1142-Fabrizio Garghetti, Eugenio Miccini, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1143-Enrico Mascelloni, Martina Corgnati, X, Sarenco, X (Box 5)
  - 1144-Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni (Box 5)
  - 1145-Eugenio Miccini, X, Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni (Box 5)
  - 1146-Valerio Dehò, Enrico Mascelloni, X, Sarenco, Carlo Palli (Box 5)
  - 1147-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1148-Sarenco, X (Box 5)
  - 1149-E.M. De Melo e Castro, Sarenco, X, Enrico Mascelloni (Box 5)
  - 1150-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1151-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1152-Una mostra di Sarenco al Castello di Umbertide (Box 5)
  - 1153-Una performance di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1154-Una performance di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1155-Una performance di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1156-Una performance di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1157-Una performance di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1158-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1159-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1160-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1161-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1162-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1163-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1164-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1165-Sarenco e Julien Blaine in performance (Box 5)
  - 1166-X, Enrico Mascelloni, X, Karel Trinkewitz, Sarenco, Grazia Azzali (Box 5)
  - 1167-X, Enrico Mascelloni, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1168-Bernard Aubertin, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1169-Sarenco, Lucia Marcucci, X, Bernard Aubertin, William Xerra, Alain Arias-Misson, Giovanni Fontana (Box 5)
  - 1170-Lamberto Pignotti, Sarenco, Lucia Marcucci, X, Bernard Aubertin, William Xerra (Box 5)
  - 1171-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1172-Julien Blaine, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1173-Sarenco: performance RECTO-VERSO, 1979 (Box 5)
  - 1174-Monty Cantsin: Performance (Box 5)
  - 1175-Monty Cantsin: Performance (Box 5)
  - 1176-Monty Cantsin: Performance (Box 5)
  - 1177-Monty Cantsin: Performance (Box 5)
  - 1178-Geoff Hendricks, Diego Strazzaer, Jean-François Bory. Jacques Donguy (Box 5)
  - 1179-Jean-François Bory e Sarenco in Verona with friends (Box 5)
  - 1180-Georg Jappe (Box 5)
  - 1181-Jean-François Bory e Sarenco in Verona with friends (Box 5)
  - 1182-Jean-François Bory and Sarenco in Verona with friends (Box 5)
  - 1183-Jean-François Bory and Sarenco in Verona with friends (Box 5)
  - 1184-Sarenco in performance (Box 5)
  - 1185-Sarenco and others exhibition in Barcelona (Box 5)
  - 1186-Sarenco, Ramon Salvo, Fernando Millan, Ladislav Novak (Box 5)
  - 1187-Fernando Millan con una sua opera (Box 5)
  - 1188-Fernando Millan con una sua opera (Box 5)
  - 1189-Ramon Salvo, Fernando Millan, Ladislav Novak (Box 5)
  - 1190-Fernando Millan e Ladislav Novak (Box 5)
  - 1191-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1192-Eugenio Miccini, X, Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, X (Box 5)
  - 1193-Eugenio Miccini, X, Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, X (Box 5)
  - 1194-Eugenio Miccini, X, Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni (Box 5)
  - 1195-Eugenio Miccini, X, Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, X (Box 5)
  - 1196-Eugenio Miccini, X, Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, X (Box 5)
  - 1197-Eugenio Miccini, X, Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, X (Box 5)
  - 1198-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1199-Sarenco, Fabrizio Garghetti (Box 5)
  - 1200-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1201-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1202-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1203-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1204-X, Sarenco, Ugo Carrega, Fernando Millan (Box 5)
  - 1205-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1206-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1207-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1208-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1209-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1210-Eugenio Miccini, X, Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, X (Box 5)
  - 1211-Eugenio Miccini, X, Enrico Mascelloni, X (Box 5)
  - 1212-Eugenio Miccini, X, Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, X (Box 5)
  - 1213-X, X, Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni (Box 5)
  - 1214-Ugo Carrega, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1215-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1216-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1217-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1218-Una scultura di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1219-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1220-Una scultura di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1221-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1222-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1223-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1224-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1225-Ladislav Novak e una sua opera (Box 5)
  - 1226-Ladislav Novak and landscape (Box 5)
  - 1227-Ladislav Novak e una sua opera (Box 5)
  - 1228-Ladislav Novak and landscape (Box 5)
  - 1229-Ladislav Novak and landscape (Box 5)
  - 1230-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1231-Sarenco, X (Box 5)
  - 1232-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1232-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1233-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1234-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1235-Sarenco in mostra a Barcellona (Box 5)
  - 1236-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1237-Un'installazione di Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1238-Jacques Donguy, Herman Nitsch, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1239-Jacques Donguy, Herman Nitsch, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1240-Herman Nitsch, Jacques Donguy, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1241-X, X, Frau Nitsch, Herman Nitsch, Sarenco, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1242-Sarenco, Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1243-Sirio Lughinbul, Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1244-Frau Nitsch, Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1245-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1246-Herman Nitsch, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1247-Herman Nitsch, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1248-Herman Nitsch, Beppe Morra, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1249-Beppe Morra, Herman Nitsch, Sarenco, X (Box 5)
  - 1250-Sarenco, Herman Nitsch, X,X,X,X (Box 5)
  - 1251-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1252-Un'opera di Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1253-Installazione di Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1254-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1255-Sirio Luginbul, Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1256-Sirio Luginbul, Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1257-Georg Jappe (Box 5)
  - 1258-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1259-Sirio Luginbul, Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1260-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1261-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1262-X, Bogdanka Poznanovic, X (Box 5)
  - 1263-Pierre Garnier (Box 5)
  - 1264-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1265-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1266-Sarenco with Mau Mau Freedom Fighters (Box 5)
  - 1267-Cheff Mwai, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1268-Herman Nitsch, Frau Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1269-Herman Nitsch, Frau Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1270-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1271-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1272-Sarenco, Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1273-Sarenco, Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1274-Sarenco, Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1275-Herman Nitsch, Beppe Morra, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1276-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1277-Beppe Morra, Herman Nitsch, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1278-Ezio Michelotti, Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1279-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1280-Performance di Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1281-Sarenco fishing (Box 5)
  - 1282-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1283-X in the installation of Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1284-X in the installation of Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1285-Performance di Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1286-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1287-Ezio Michelotti, Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1288-Sarenco in Anfo, 1968 (Box 5)
  - 1289-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1290-From a Sarenco's movie (Box 5)
  - 1291-Georg Jappe (Box 5)
  - 1292-Sarenco, J.M. Calleja, Julien Blaine, Fernando Millan, Eugenio Miccini (Box 5)
  - 1293-Sarenco in performance con la figlia Eva (Box 5)
  - 1294-Aldo Mondino (Box 5)
  - 1295-Fernando Millan (Box 5)
  - 1296-Jean-François Bory (Box 5)
  - 1297-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1298-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1299-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1300-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1301-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1302-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1303-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1304-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1305-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1306-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1307-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1308-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1309-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1310-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1311-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1312-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1313-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1314-Eric Pittard, Vittorio Gelmetti, Aldo Mondino, Patrizia Guerresi,X, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1315-Patrizia Guerresi, Eric Pittard, Vittorio Gelmetti, Aldo Mondino, X, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1316-Sarenco, Eric Pittard, Vittorio Gelmetti, Patrizia Guerresi (Box 5)
  - 1317-Eric Pittard, Vittorio Gelmetti, Aldo Mondino, Patrizia Guerresi, X, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1318-Patrizia Guerresi, Eric Pittard, Vittorio Gelmetti, Aldo Mondino, X, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1319-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1320-Sarenco's movie (Box 5)
  - 1321-Sarenco's movie (Box 5)
  - 1322-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 5)
  - 1323-Herman Nitsch (Box 5)
  - 1324-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1325-Sarenco fishing (Box 5)
  - 1326-Sarenco in Buenos Aires (Box 5)
  - 1327-Sarenco in La Plata with Edgardo A. Vigo family (Box 5)
  - 1328-Patrizia Guerresi, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1329-Sarenco, X, Patrizia Guerresi (Box 5)
  - 1330-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1331-Un'installazione di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1332-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1333-Sarenco, Richard Onyango (Box 5)
  - 1334-Sarenco, George Lilanga, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1335-X in una installazione di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1336-Sarenco's performance con la figlia Eva (Box 5)
  - 1337-Sarenco's performance (Box 5)
  - 1338-Sarenco's performance (Box 5)
  - 1339-Sarenco's performance (Box 5)
  - 1340-Sarenco's performance (Box 5)
  - 1341-Sarenco's performance (Box 5)
  - 1342-Sarenco's performance (Box 5)
  - 1343-Sarenco's performance (Box 5)
  - 1344-Sarenco's found artwork (Box 5)
  - 1345-Paolo Berardelli, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1346-X, Julien Blaine, X (Box 5)
  - 1347-Giovanni Fontana, Sarenco, Paolo Berardelli (Box 5)
  - 1348-Giovanni Fontana, Sarenco, Paolo Berardelli (Box 5)
  - 1349-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1350-Sarenco's performance (Box 5)
  - 1351-Sarenco's performance (Box 5)
  - 1352-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1353-Ugo Carrega, Wladimiro Tulli, Julien Blaine,Vinicio Berti, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1354-Ugo Carrega, Wladimiro Tulli, Julien Blaine, Vinicio Berti, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1355-Jean-François Bory, X (Box 5)
  - 1356-Sarenco's performance (Box 5)
  - 1357-Wladimiro Tulli, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1358-Sarenco, Francesco Conz (Box 5)
  - 1359-Adriana Casu, Bartolomé Ferrando (Box 5)
  - 1360-Bruno Munari, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1361-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1362-Bruno Munari, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1363-Bruno Munari, Sarenco, Aldo Mondino, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1364-Bruno Munari, Aldo Mondino, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1365-Bogdanka Poznanovic (Box 5)
  - 1366-X, Bogdanka Poznanovic, X (Box 5)
  - 1367-Patrizia Guerresi, X, X, X (Box 5)
  - 1368-Sarenco, Bruno Munari (Box 5)
  - 1369-Sarenco, Aldo Mondino, Bruno Munari (Box 5)
  - 1370-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1371-Sarenco's performance in Anfo, 1968 (Box 5)
  - 1372-Bruno Munari, Sarenco, X (Box 5)
  - 1373-Bruno Munari, Sarenco, X,X (Box 5)
  - 1374-Bruno Munari, Sarenco, X (Box 5)
  - 1375-Bruno Munari, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1376-X, Lamberto Pignotti (Box 5)
  - 1377-X, Lamberto Pignotti (Box 5)
  - 1378-Lamberto Pignotti (Box 5)
  - 1379-Julien Blaine, X, Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1380-Da un film di Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1381-Adriano Parise, Aldo Mondino (Box 5)
  - 1382-Sarenco (Box 5)
  - 1383-Aldo Mondino, Sarenco, Adriano Parise (Box 5)
  - 1384-Sarenco, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1385-Innocente, Aldo Mondino, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1386-Sarenco, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1387-Sarenco, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1388-Sarenco, Vittorio Gelmetti, X, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1389-Un'opera di Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1390-Un'opera di Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1391-Un'opera di Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1392-Un'opera di Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1393-Un'opera di Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1394-Un'opera di Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1395-Sarenco, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1396-Un'opera di Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1397-Un'opera di Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1398-Un'opera di Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1399-Sarenco, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1400-Aldo Mondino, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1401-Aldo Mondno, Sarenco, X (Box 6)
  - 1402-Sarenco Auguste Galli, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1403-Sarenco, Vittorio Gelmetti, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1404-Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1405-X, X, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1406-Adriano Parise, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1407-Paolo Berardelli, Sarenco, Giorgio Cortenova, Aldo Mondino, Ignazio Moncada (Box 6)
  - 1408-Un'opera di Georg Jappe (Box 6)
  - 1409-Georg Jappe (Box 6)
  - 1410-Georg Jappe (Box 6)
  - 1411-Georg Jappe (Box 6)
  - 1412-Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1413-Sarenco, X, Patrizia Guerresi (Box 6)
  - 1414-Sarenco con una sua installazione (Box 6)
  - 1415-Sarenco, X, Enrico Mascelloni (Box 6)
  - 1416-Patrizia Guerresi, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1417-Vaclav Havel (Box 6)
  - 1418-Jacques Donguy, Herman Nitsch, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1419-Sarenco in Anfo, 1968 (Box 6)
  - 1420-Sarenco performance in Anfo, 1968 (Box 6)
  - 1421-Sarenco in Venezia (Box 6)
  - 1422-Fabrizio Garghetti, Ladislav Novak, X, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1423-Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1424-Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1425-George Lilanga, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1426-Silvana Zambanini in un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1427-Giuseppe Desiato, Bernard Aubertin, Sarenco, Patrizia Guerresi (Box 6)
  - 1428-Sarenco's performance (Box 6)
  - 1429-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1430-Performance di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1431-Beppe Morra (Box 6)
  - 1432-X, Richard Onyango, Jean Pigozzi, André Magnin, X, Sarenco in Venezia (Box 6)
  - 1433-Sarenco nella sua installazione alla Biennale di Venezia 2001 (Box 6)
  - 1434-Monty Cantsin (Box 6)
  - 1435-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1436-X, Fernando Millan (Box 6)
  - 1437-Sarenco nella sua installazione alla Biennale di Venezia 2001 (Box 6)
  - 1438-Sarenco and Mau Mau freedom fighters (Box 6)
  - 1439-Un'installazione di Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1440-Due opere di Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1441-Monty Cantsin (Box 6)
  - 1442-Un'installazione di Monty Cantsin (Box 6)
  - 1443-Sarenco e Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1444-Jean-François Bory e Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1445-Patrizia Guerresi in una mostra di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1446-Sarenco, Bruno Munari (Box 6)
  - 1447-Bruno Munari, Sarenco, X (Box 6)
  - 1448-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1449-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1450-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1451-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1452-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1453-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1454-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 6)
  - 1455-Elidio De Paoli, Aldo Mondino, Sarenco, Ambasciatore russo in Italia, X (Box 6)
  - 1456-Hermann Nitsch (Box 6)
  - 1457-Jacques Donguy, Hermann Nitsch, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1458-Jacques Donguy, Sarenco, Hermann Nitsch (Box 6)
  - 1459-Hermann Nitsch, X, Sarenco, Frau Nitsch (Box 6)
  - 1460-Hermann Nitsch, X, Sarenco, Frau Nitsch (Box 6)
  - 1461-Sarenco, Hermann Nitsch, Lamberto Pignotti (Box 6)
  - 1462-X, X, Hermann Nitsch, Geoff Hendricks, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1463-Frau Nitsch, Hermann Nitsch (Box 6)
  - 1464-Sirio Luginbuhl, Hermann Nitsch (Box 6)
  - 1465-Sarenco and Mau Mau freedom fighters (Box 6)
  - 1466-X, Fernando Millan (Box 6)
  - 1467-Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1468-Monty Cantsin (Box 6)
  - 1469-Sarenco, Monty Cantsin (Box 6)
  - 1470-Monty Cantsin, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1471-Shimamoto performance (Box 6)
  - 1472-Shozo Shimamoto performance (Box 6)
  - 1473-Jean-François Bory, Jochen Gerz, Ugo Carrega, Alain Arias-Misson (Box 6)
  - 1474-Sarenco, Antonella Montenovesi, Jean-François Bory, Eugenio Miccini, Alain Arias-Misson (Box 6)
  - 1475-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1476-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1477-Jean-François Bory, Sarenco, Gigliola Fazzini (Box 6)
  - 1478-Un'opera di Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1479-Un'installazione di Sarenco (Box 6)